我母亲已经好些了  市长
Mother is better now, Mayor.
再次感谢
And thanks again.
我知道家里有急事总是很麻烦的
I know family emergencies are never convenient.
但是经过自我反思之后
But after some personal reflection,
认为我还是需要陪着她
I realized I have to be with her.
毕竟她给了我生命
Everything I am started with her.
你确定没被跟踪吗
You sure you weren't followed?
-是的  -很好
- Yes. - Good.
您改变了装束
You've changed your appearance.
这套衣服是必要的
The suit is necessary.
它其中含有的特质能帮助我
The properties inside of it help me continue
在离开镜像协调室之后
my acclimation process
持续适应的过程
when I'm outside the reflection modulation chamber.
现在
Now...
是时候除掉我丈夫了
It's time to get rid of my husband.
我们就从除掉一切保护他的事物开始
We begin by dismantling everything that protects him.
你知道该从哪里开始
You know where to start.
保证成功
Success is assured.
闪 电 侠
闪电侠
第六季  第十九集
各位  目前爱瑞丝  卡米拉  还有辛格
Guys, shouldn't it be all hands on desk
都被困在镜像宇宙里
with Iris, Kamilla, and Singh
每个人不该出份力吗
stuck in the Mirrorverse?
听着  你的情况和他们一样重要
Hey, you're just as important.
凯特琳女士  或者冰霜  这件行吗
Uh, Ms. Caitlin? Or Frost?
他们要去北极  不是去奥兹音乐节
Uh, they're going to the Arctic, not Ozz-fest.
世界最大的金属音乐节
你怎么什么都干不好
How are you so bad at everything?
凯特琳把我们的厚外套收在后面的衣橱里
Caity keeps our heavy coats in the back closet.
我去找
I'll check on it.
好的  那更合理点
Right. That makes more sense.
你对这些事情很擅长
You're so good at this kind of stuff--
这么生我气
so mad at me.
确实有点生气
Little bit. Mm.
纳什  阿莱格拉最终会回心转意的
Nash, Allegra will come around eventually.
你一定要坚持到那一刻
You just have to be there when she does.
对这个过程要有信心
Trust the process.
作为一根冰棍你还挺睿智的
Pretty wise for a popsicle.
谢了  我可是有一份德比证书呢
Thanks. Got a Dib-ploma to prove it.
真好笑
Ba-dum-bum.
很酷
Uh...cool.
-能借我穿吗  -当然
- Can I borrow this? - Sure.
我会很想你的
I'm really gonna miss you.
-我也是  -什么
- Me too. - Hmm?
我是说  我们都会想你的
I mean, all--we all are.
真贴心  你还有得救
Aww. There's hope for you yet.
行了  好了
Enough. Okay.
你要好好的
You stay frosty.
我没事
I'm fine.
不  你有事
No, you're not.
亲爱的  这都是正常的
And honey, it's okay.
我跟你保证  你能应对一切情况
I promise you you can handle anything.
你要记得  她也是你的母亲
You just gotta remember. She's your mom too.
我当然是
Of course I am.
你好  冰霜杀手
Hi, Killer Frost.
现在只是冰霜了
it's just Frost now.
好了
Okay, um.
我们不打扰你们俩了
We're gonna leave you two alone.
你在北方安顿下来后给我们打个电话
Give us a call when you get settled in the north.
给他们点厉害瞧瞧
Give 'em hell.
那么...
So...
我觉得应该在离开之前先做一些测试
I, um, I think I should run a few tests before we leave.
检查下你的核糖核酸异常基线
Check your baseline for any ribonucleic anomalies.
好的
Great.
伊娃已经失踪超过24小时了
Eva's been missing for over 24 hours.
面部识别有什么进展吗
Where are we with facial recognition?
卫星一无所获
Satellites have turned up zilch.
人造的神速力还没完成
The Artificial Speed Force isn't finished yet,
所以我还是不能像往常一样搜寻整座城市
so I still can't do my usual sweeps of the city.
好吧  我们为什么要在这里见面
Right. Uh, why are we meeting here?
我有一大堆积压的案子
I have a backlog of cases.
我不能再失去我犯罪现场鉴证员的工作了
I can't lose my CSI job along with everything else.
工作
A job...
伊娃说她有没处理完的事
Eva said that she had unfinished business.
有没有可能她说的就是工作
Is there any way that she meant that literally?
如果她想要麦克洛奇回来
Oh, if she wants to get McCulloch back,
她确实需要对付黑洞
she does have to deal with Black Hole.
那找到黑洞  就能找到伊娃
So find Black Hole, find Eva.
-知道从哪里查起吗  -不知道
- Any idea where to start? - Actually, no.
或许我知道
Maybe.
-拉尔夫  -拉尔夫
- Ralph. - Ralph.
-你从哪儿弄来的  -你从哪儿弄来的
- Where'd you get that? - Where'd you get that?
-苏给我的  -她给你的吗
- Sue gave it to me. - She gave you that?
-她给你的吗  -是她给我的
- She gave that to you? - She gave that to me.
结果黑洞的标志被刻在了里面
And it turns out that Black Hole's logo is embedded inside.
老兄  那东西正在释放大量的紫外线能量
Dude, there's serious UV energy coming off that thing.
我能看看吗
Can I?
这是个三角测量地图
This is a Triangulation Cartograph.
这是一张藏宝图
It's a treasure map.
阿莱格拉  对准这个
Allegra. Aim it over this.
中心是在42街和达尔比街交汇
The center's at 42nd and Darby.
等等
Hang on.
42街和达尔比街交汇
42nd and Darby...
-见鬼了  -怎么了
- Holy heck. - What?
那是一个有地下五层的
Well, it turns out that is a ginormous warehouse
巨大仓库
with five subterranean levels.
拉尔夫和我去看看
Ralph and I will check it out.
你俩负责通讯
You two take comms.
我就...  打扰了
Let me just--excuse me.
会是个漫长的夜晚
Could be a long night.
我做了两杯咖啡
I made us a couple of coffees.
-我讨厌咖啡  -不喝咖啡
- I hate coffee. - No coffee.
伙计们  我们进去了
Guys, we're in.
好的  注意安全
All right. Be careful.
-那样的地方可能有一两个保安  -应该是五个
- Place like that could have a guard or two. - More like five.
他们都被刺了
They were all stabbed.
我猜用的是镜子刺刀
By a mirror-bayonet, I'm guessing.
这里坏人的玩意还挺多
That is a lot of bad-guy stuff.
这是黑洞的储藏所
It's Black Hole's depository.
迪尔邦
苏说过卡夫在勒索她的父母
Sue said that Carver was blackmailing her parents.
这是银行对账单
This is bank statements,
投资记录
investment records.
这一定是卡夫所拥有的全部把柄
This must be everything that Carver has on them.
-我要把这个拿走  -好
- I'm taking this. - All right.
这里闻起来有汽油味
It smells like gasoline in here.
辛格
Singh.
我不想再伤害任何人了
I don't wanna hurt anyone else.
跟那些你杀死的守卫说去
Tell that to those guards you killed.
他们让我无从选择
They left me no choice.
我必须保证伊娃的成功
I have to assure Eva's success.
放下喷火枪
Just put down the flare gun.
帮助我们将卡夫正法
Help us bring Carver to justice.
母亲对你所谓的正义不感兴趣
Mother's not interested in your brand of justice.
辛格  辛格
Singh. Singh!
这不是你
This isn't you.
你还是没明白  是吧
You still don't get it, do you?
卡夫那晚就在那里
Carver was there that night.
他任由镜子困住她
He let the mirror keep her.
他从没有想救她
He never tried to rescue her.
相反  他把她的科技高价卖出
Instead, he sold her tech to the highest bidder.
做武器  勒索  甚至更糟
For weapons, blackmail, or worse.
这就是为什么卡夫
And that is why Carver
死定了
is a dead man.
不起作用
Uh, not working.
各位
Guys?
艾伦  德比  你们还在吗
Allen, Dibny, are you guys there?
勉强
Barely.
我们现在怎么办
What do we do now?
唯一能做的
The only thing we can.
保护卡夫
Protect Carver.
我们的人知道要毁掉任何
And our guy knows to destroy anything
能让我与仓库产生联系的东西吧
that could tie me to the warehouse?
是  但是也没剩什么能毁的了
Yes, but there's nothing left to destroy.
所有东西都烧掉了
Everything we had was incinerated.
替换那些物品
Replace the items.
要迅速安静
Quickly and quietly.
别用那三人
Don't use The Three.
不能让他们知道自己解放了
They can't know they're off leash.
如果有人要冲我来
If someone is coming after me,
我会需要他们的保护
I'll need their protection.
你好啊  艾伦警官
Hello. Officer Allen.
请吧
Please.
你不是来扇我的吧
You're not here to slap me, are you?
韦斯特队长扇了左边
Captain West went for the left side.
话说  他怎么样了
How is he, by the way?
这种事没法往轻松了说  所以...
Look, there's no easy way to say this, so...
你的妻子想杀你
Your wife wants to kill you.
但是中城警局无法保证你的安全
But CCPD can't keep you safe.
我妻子已经死了
My wife is dead.
伊娃被困在另一个维度
Eva's been trapped in another dimension
已经六年了
for the last six years.
那地方叫镜像宇宙
Place called the Mirrorverse.
但你早就知道了
But you already knew that.
如果伊娃真的逃离了那个鬼地方  我会知道
If Eva did escape that wretched place, I'd know.
事关你妻子  对吗
This is about your wife, isn't it?
几周前  我在我妻子的办公室里
I came across this footage
发现了这段录像
from my wife's office a couple of weeks ago.
你知道爱瑞丝被绑架了
You knew Iris was abducted?
你妻子有麻烦了
Your wife was a problem.
她的失踪很偶然
Her disappearance was fortuitous.
我妻子怎么了
What happened to my wife?
她的遭遇和我的伊娃一样
The same thing that happened to my Eva.
她不在了  她们都不在了
She's gone. They both are.
不
No.
肯定会有办法带她回来的
There has to be a way to get her back.
我以前也是这么想的
I used to think that too.
但如果爱瑞丝在那里还活着
But if Iris is still alive in there,
她已经无法被拯救了
there's probably nothing left of her to save.
我让世上最顶尖的人才去研究那个
I had the most brilliant minds in the world study that...
镜像宇宙
Mirrorverse.
你知道他们发现了什么吗
You know what they found?
它与人类的大脑无法兼容
It's incompatible with the human brain.
那个地方使人精神错乱
That place warps the mind
直到这个人变得认不出来
until the person is no longer recognizable.
你的爱瑞丝
Your Iris
早就不在了
is long gone.
我建议你接受现实
I suggest you accept that
继续生活
and move on.
还有一件事
Oh, so one more thing.
你怎么知道伊娃在追杀我
How do you know Eva's coming after me?
还有谁会烧了你的仓库
Who else would've burnt down your warehouse?
42街和达尔比街交汇  对吗
42nd and Darby, right?
我从没在城里那边买过仓库
I'd never buy on that side of town.
我不需要保护
And I don't need protecting.
代我向韦斯特队长问好
You give Captain West my best.
如果没有卫星
Without the satellites,
要想找到辛格局长基本不可能
finding Chief Singh feels impossible.
我知道
I know.
我们得自己去找他了
We'll have to go find him ourselves.
我每次和这个地方有所感应
Every time I interact with this place,
神经失调就会越来越严重
the neural dissonance gets worse.
如果伊娃回来了呢
And what if Eva comes back?
然后呢
Then what?
听着
Look.
虽然这个地方的东西都是反着的
Things in this place may be backwards,
但一切都还能用
but everything works.
我们只需要找到方法
We just--we just have to figure out how.
检测到热能
温度  98.9
你看到城市的地图了吗
Did you see the map of the city?
你才说过看那些东西太危险了
You just said looking at those was too dangerous.
不  我不是故意的
No, I didn't mean to,
但我刚才正在想找大卫的事
but I was thinking about finding David,
地图就出现了
and the map came into view.
有来自一个特定地方的热能
There--there was thermal energy coming from a specific place.
我不知道具体是哪  但一定是大卫
I'm not sure where, but that has to be David.
像是有一个范围  几乎像个灯塔
There was like a--a radius, almost like a beacon.
我感觉如果我能集中注意力
I--I feel like if I could just focus,
我就能找到这个位置
I could--I can find his location.
不  爱瑞丝  看看你
No, Iris. Come on, look at you!
不  我正在适应这个地方  卡米拉
No, I'm acclimating to this place, Kamilla.
这就是为什么我能看到地图而你不能
That's why I can see the map and you can't.
我能找到大卫
I can find David.
-迪尔邦夫人  -你好
- Mrs. Dearbon. - Hi.
迪尔邦先生  很高兴再次见到你
Mr. Dearbon, so great to see you again.
我有绝好的消息
I have fantastic news.
结果发现
So it turns out that s--
所以你就是我父母雇的
So you are the person
找我的那个人
that my parents employed to find me.
见到你很高兴
It's so good to meet you.
请原谅我
And please forgive me.
我从没想造成麻烦
I--I never meant to cause a stir.
我读了《恋爱  美食  祈祷》
I read "Eat, Pray, Love,"
我对于祈祷那部分有点过于认真
and I took the pray part just a little bit too seriously.
我们苏西在印度参加了一个意识静修活动
Our Susie joined a mindfulness retreat in India.
我本打算待一个月
I meant to stay for a month
结果忘记了时间  待了几周又几个月
and then lost track of the weeks, months.
时有发生  对吧
Happens, right?
德比先生  我们很高兴
Mr. Dibny, while we're delighted
我们的苏西回来了
to have our Susie back,
但我们也知道到你费了多大功夫
we realize how much trouble you went to.
你有笔吗
Do you have a pen?
见鬼  真想不到
Oh, heck. Wouldn't you know?
我刚用完了
I'm fresh out.
让我看看走廊的柜子里有没
Let me just check that hallway closet.
-迪尔邦夫人能帮我找支笔吗  -当然
- Ms. Dearbon, could you help me look for a pen? - Of course.
我们一会回来
We'll be right back.
你需要信笺簿之类的吗
You need a legal pad or anything?
你为什么给我父母打电话
Why would you call my parents?
你给我的钻石
So that diamond that you gave me, it turns out
结果里面有黑洞仓库的地图
that it has a map for Black Hole's stash house.
我做了点侦查
I did some recon.
我以为非法入侵
I thought breaking and entering
是伸缩人不会跨越的红线
was a line Elongated Man didn't cross.
你能  小点声吗
Will you-- inside voices please.
-对不起  -看
- Oh, I'm sorry. - Look.
卡弗之前有关于你父母的文件
Carver had files with your parents names on them.
那些文件含有
Those files contain the evidence
他用来敲诈你父母的证据
he was using to extort them.
之前是什么意思
What do you mean "Had"?
事情有点焦灼
Things got toasty,
卡弗的敲诈军工厂被烧了
and Carver's blackmail arsenal got cooked.
你点着了那里
You torched the place?
不  我
No. I--no.
我该怎么说
Okay. How do I say this?
有一个镜像宇宙
There's a Mirrorverse dimension.
到处都是举止古怪的人
There's these pod people running around.
他们会杀死无辜的人
They're claiming innocent lives.
就像是《人体异形》里那样
It's very "Invasion of the Bodies."
不如这样
You know what?
我们忘了刚刚说的那些吧
Why don't we just forget about that part?
重点是你父母现在很安全
The point is your parents are safe.
没错  我知道
Yeah. I already knew that.
不用谢  这没什么
Well, you're welcome. It was really no--
等等  什么
Wait. What?
卡弗上周给我打了电话
Yeah, Carver called last week.
说他改变主意了
Said he had a change of heart.
卡弗这种人不会轻易改变主意
Guys like Carver don't have hearts to change.
我同意
Agreed.
但是我父母安全了
But my parents are safe,
我终于可以回家了
and I can finally go home.
我不明白  如果我们一致认为
I don't understand. If we agreed--
够了  滑头
Enough, slick.
你真的想要帮我吗
You really wanna help me?
那就别来打扰我们了
Leave us in peace.
卡弗十五分钟后到
他说了是谁想要他的命吗
Did he say who wants his head on a pike now?
烈日去哪里了
谁在乎这个
她总会出现的
她一直是这样
是谁
Who's there?
你好  纪美代
Hello, Kimiyo.
你是想来的轻松一点
Shall we do this the easy way...
还是痛苦一点
Or the hard way?
烈日
Sunshine?
霍西
Hoshi?
致命紫光
Ultraviolet?
我很高兴卡弗拒绝了你
I'm glad Carver turned you down.
在他对我表姐  乔和爱瑞丝做了那些事后
After what he did to my cousin, Joe, Iris,
他是罪有应得
he deserves what he gets.
他罪不至死
He doesn't deserve to die.
如果他说的是实话呢
What if he's telling the truth
镜像宇宙会影响大脑
about the Mirrorverse affecting minds?
或者他在说谎
Or he's lying.
他又不是诚实完人
He's not exactly the paragon of truth.
我认为他没有说谎
I don't think he's lying.
我认为可能是神经失调
I think it could be neural dissonance.
我想起旅行时见过的一个地球
I came across this Earth on my travels
在那里任何外来访客都会立即陷入
where any visitor to that Earth immediately suffers
一种创伤性心理状态
a traumatic psychological state.
就是神经失调
Neural dissonance.
有可能是这种情况
This could be that.
很高兴有人相信我
I'm glad someone believes me.
我终究还是需要你的帮助  艾伦
I need your help after all, Allen.
联邦保护
Federal Protection.
和乔·韦斯特一样的待遇
The full Joe West treatment.
你那些杀手爪牙去哪里了
What happened to your killer minions?
伊娃先找到他们了  是吗
Eva got to them first, didn't she?
你到底帮不帮我
You gonna help me or not?
听着  把我纳入证人保护计划
Look, get me into protection,
乔就可以出来了
and Joe can get out of it.
只要我一个电话
One call from me
他今晚就可以在自己的床上睡觉了
and he's sleeping in his own bed tonight.
你还真够极品的  知道吗
You're a real piece of work. You know that?
这听着像答应我了
That sounded like a yes to me.
有意思
That's interesting.
化学计量比的显示
The stoichiometric ratio is manifesting
是不正常的
in a way that's abnormal.
如果凯特琳能在这里
It'd be so much easier
帮忙分析就简单多了
if Caitlin were here to help analyze.
我能帮忙
I could help.
对不起
Oh, I'm--I'm sorry.
我只是说我需要一个
I just--I just meant that I could use
超能力DNA专家的帮助
an expert in meta-DNA.
我忘了
I forgot.
我想通了
I figured.
可能因为你一看到我
Probably because every time you look at me,
就会看到托马斯
you just see Thomas
和他变成的那个怪物
and the monster he became.
你不是怪物
You're not a monster.
你保护了凯特琳免受她父亲的伤害
You protected Caitlin from her father and then some,
而且远不止这些  比我做的要多得多
which is a hell of a lot more than I ever did.
说实话
You know, to be honest,
我总觉得自己像个电灯泡
I always kind of felt like a third wheel.
很抱歉让你有这种感觉
I'm sorry you felt that way.
不  不
No. No.
这一定很可怕
It must have been horrible.
但话说回来  我这辈子
Then again, I've...
犯了太多的错
made so many mistakes in my life.
也许我才是需要挽救的那个人
Maybe--maybe I'm the one who needs fixing.
你是位杰出的科学家
You're a brilliant scientist
管理着地球上最成功的实验室
who runs the most successful lab on the planet.
我觉得你不需要挽救
I don't think you need fixing.
因为在我看来
'Cause from where I'm standing,
你是个相当出色的人
you're a pretty awesome human being.
一个我想去更多了解的人
One I'd like to get to know a lot better.
我也想更多了解你
I'd like that too.
怎么耽搁了这么久
What is taking so long?
联邦探员随时会来
Uh, federal agents will be here any minute
将你收押
to take you into custody.
警官  卡弗先生
Officer. Mr. Carver.
当你的资料出现在我桌上时
When your paperwork came across my desk,
我觉得你这样的贵宾
I thought a VIP such as yourself
不应该乘坐廉价的政府小货车
shouldn't have to ride in a two-bit government van.
所以我亲自来护送你去收押
So I'm here to escort you personally into custody.
艾伦  来聊两句
Allen, a word?
让我把卡弗从这里带走
Let me walk out of here with Carver,
母亲就会把爱瑞丝给你
and Mother will give you Iris.
伊娃没兴趣跟你或
Eva is not interesting in a fight with you
你的朋友斗
or with your friends.
你知道你放火烧那个仓库时
You knew we were in that warehouse
我们也在场
when you set it on fire.
那对我来说就是挑起斗争
That feels like a fight to me.
把他交给我  巴里
Let me have him, Barry.
他是坏人
He's a bad man.
带爱瑞丝回家
Bring Iris home.
找回你自己的生活
Get your life back.
我们到底还干不干了
Are we doing this or what?
到我身后
On my six!
干什么
What the hell?
有人能告诉我到底发生了什么吗
Will someone please tell me what the hell is going on?
我救了你  就这么回事
I saved you. That's what's going on.
-纳什  -什么
- Nash. - What?
我认识的巴里·艾伦
The Barry Allen I know
永远不  永远不会考虑那个提议
would never, never have considered that deal.
我知道伊娃很有野心
I knew Eva was ambitious,
但是镜像复制人
but Mirror Duplicates.
伊娃比你想象的要强大
Eva's more powerful than you thought.
我没明白
I don't get it.
为什么她不自己直接冲你来
Why doesn't she just come after you herself?
伊娃名义上还是失踪的
Well, Eva's still technically missing,
所以她不能被公众发现
so she can't be seen in public.
这就是为什么她带走了辛格
That's why she took Singh.
警局的局长可以接近你
The chief of police could get close to you.
幸运的是  威尔斯先生把我们传送到安全的地方
Fortunately, Mr. Wells teleported us to safety.
不客气
You're welcome.
那是什么设备
What is that device?
你开个价吧
And how much do you want for it?
那是非卖品  人渣
It's not for sale, dirtbag.
行啦
Oh, please.
每个人都有标价
Everyone has a price.
听着  我们刚刚救了你
Hey, listen. We just saved your keister.
所以为什么你不能闭上嘴
So why don't you put a sock in it
直到我们决定好怎么处理你
till we can figure out what to do with you?
所以看来我们要和我们的新客人共处一段时间了
So guess we're stuck with our new guest for a while.
用不了多久伊娃就会出现在这
It's only a matter of time before Eva shows up here.
是啊
Right.
尖端科研实验室里的任何一面镜子
Any mirrored surface inside S.T.A.R. Labs
都有可能是她通过的门
is a door for her to walk through.
麦克洛奇安保系统可以保护我们
McCulloch security system can protect us.
我有个伊娃不知道的安全屋
I have a panic room Eva doesn't know about.
无意冒犯  但是更多的警卫和一个密室
No offense, but extra guards and a locked den
可帮不到我们
aren't gonna help us out here.
我有个生物基因电离场
I have a biogenic ionization field
可以在整个场地周围激活
that can be activated around the entire facility.
任何闯入的东西都会在一秒内被粉碎
Anything breaking in would be atomized in a second.
我们只需要过去
We just have to get there.
我们可以走下水道系统
We could take the sewer system.
从研发部门下面过去
Pop over underneath R and D?
我总闯来闯去
I break into things.
择日不如撞日
No time like the present?
艾伦
Allen.
我想问你个问题
I wanna ask you a question.
你知道镜像辛格一走下电梯
You knew that Carver was in mortal danger, right,
卡夫就处于生命危险  是吧
as soon as Mirror-Singh stepped off that elevator.
你为什么不把他带离那里
Why didn't you get him out of there?
我没法以巴里·艾伦的身份带他出去
I couldn't exactly run him out of there as Barry Allen.
也可能是他提出要和你做一笔交易
Or he offered you a deal.
这就是另外那件事
That's the other thing.
我脑袋里有不少威尔斯  而他们
I have all these Wells in my head, and they all--
他们都在大声地跟我说
they're all screaming the same thing,
他们认识的巴里·艾伦绝不会犹豫不决
that the Barry Allen they knew would never have hesitated.
但你犹豫了
You did.
你之前在考虑是否进行交易
You were considering the deal.
你之前在考虑用卡夫的命来换爱瑞斯的命
You were considering trading Carver's life to save Iris.
事情没有那么简单
It's more complicated than that.
-这事非常复杂...  -是啊
- It's more complicated... - Yeah.
这事的复杂程度是不是跟
Is it complicated like in the way
你差点杀了艾尔伯德·斯旺和我一样呢
you almost killed Eobard Thawne and me along with him?
-不  完全不一样  -怎么就不一样了
- No. That was different. - How is that different?
爱瑞丝是我妻子
Iris is my wife.
我必须要救她
I have to save her.
你怎么就不明白这一点呢
How do you not understand that?
我明白
I do.
但你觉得爱瑞丝会怎么说
But what do you think Iris will say
当你告诉她
when you tell her
你是用另一个人的命来救的她时
you traded another person's life to save hers?
天眼会一小时之内就会来这里逮捕你
A.R.G.U.S. will be here in an hour to take you into custody.
-等等  这里不安全  -放轻松
- Wait, this isn't safe. - Relax.
看到你妻子发生的事后
After I saw what happened to your wife,
我已经把它覆盖上了保护性纳米机器人
I had it coated with protective nanites.
我还以为帕尔默科技和麦克洛奇是对手呢
I thought Palmer Tech and McCulloch were rivals.
只能说帕尔默科技不知就无害
Let's just say what Palmer Tech doesn't know won't hurt them.
这就是我的安全屋
And this is my panic room.
四周都是混泥土墙  而且没有一面镜子
Concrete walls and not a mirror in sight.
哪怕外面的区域都沦陷了  伊娃也进不来这里
Even if my outer field fails, Eva can't get in here.
一旦整座大楼都清空了
Well, once the building's clear,
你就可以启动你的离子场了
you can engage your ion field.
那就让你的人加速完成撤离吧
Then tell your people to speed up the evacuation.
活动警告
激活力场
激活  不激活
你不必回家  但你也不能待在这里
You don't have to go home, but you can't stay here.
阿莱格拉  给你  拿好
Allegra, here. Take this.
以防万一  好吗
Just in case. All right?
万一碰上麻烦  你可以用你的紫外线引爆它
Any trouble, you should blast it with one of your UV Rays.
记住了吗  可以帮你分散对方的注意力
All right? Provide a welcome distraction.
你什么时候才能不这样费劲
When are you gonna stop trying?
永远不会
Never.
什么情况
What the hell?
我就知道你在撒谎
I knew you were lying.
你真的不能领会暗示
You really can't take a hint.
你不能来这打劫
You're not here to rob the place.
而且卡夫也并没有对你的父母改变心意
And Carver didn't have a change of heart on your parents.
你要替代他们在黑洞的位置
You--you offered to take their place in Black Hole.
卡夫同意了
Carver agrees.
我比我的父母更有价值
I'm more valuable than my parents.
苏  你
Sue, you--
你没必要这么做
you don't have to do this.
不  有必要
Yes, I do.
我一年多来都在搜集能够影响卡夫的东西
I've been trying to collect leverage on Carver for over a year.
但他密不透风
He's untouchable.
除非你有一个
Untouchable unless you have one of those
非常有用的黑洞徽章
handy-dandy Black Hole pins.
你加入黑洞是为了接近卡夫
You joined Black Hole to get close to Carver.
因为你要杀了他
Because you're gonna kill him.
这就是你来这里的原因  对吗
That's why you're here, isn't it?
卡夫绝对不会放走你的父母
Carver's never gonna let my parents go.
苏  该死
Sue, damn it--
-只有这样才能结束  -你得听我的
- It's the only way it ends. - You gotta listen to me.
总会有其他选择的
There--there is always another way.
你知道杀死卡夫会有什么后果吗
Do you understand what happens if you kill Carver?
每当你照镜子的时候
Every time you look in the mirror,
你会认不出来镜子里的人
you won't recognize the person looking back.
-你会失去自我  -关你何事
- You'll lose yourself. - Why do you care?
因为我相信你
Because I believe in you!
我知道你还有善良的一面
And I know there's still good in you.
我能看到
I can see it.
对不起了  滑头
I'm sorry about this, slick.
拜托
Oh, come on.
下面安全了
All clear down here.
力场已经准备就绪
Ready for the force field when you are.
启动力场
力场已启动  能量源激活
离子场已经启动了
The ion field's up and running.
现在只需要等着就行了
Now all that's left to do is sit and wait.
干杯
Cheers.
情况不妙
That's not good.
力场关闭  能量源受干扰
各位  力场失效了
Guys, the force field isn't working anymore.
能找出能量源出了什么问题吗
Can we find out what happened to the power source?
我们知道原因了
We know what happened.
卡夫的天使不请自来
Carver's angels invited themselves to the party.
埃斯佩兰萨  我们以为你被伊娃抓住了
不  她给了我们一个选择
卡夫从未给过我们选择
Something Carver never did.
我们不再受他控制了
We're no longer under his thumb.
伊娃也一样
Neither is Eva.
不管她付你多少钱  我都出双倍
Whatever she is paying you, I will double it.
这和报酬无关
This isn't about a paycheck.
这是为了报仇
It's about payback.
伊娃要找你来了  卡夫
Eva's coming for you, Carver.
而我们要扫清她的障碍
And we're gonna make sure no one gets in her way.
这团聚太好了
Nice family reunion!
伊娃随时都会到
Eva's gonna be here any minute.
我们要重新启动离子场
We have to get your ion field back up.
还有其他能量源吗
Is there an alternate power source?
地下室
The sub-basement.
可以远程启动备用发电机
There's remote access to a secondary generator.
大家尽量拖住他们
Guys, hold them off as long as you can.
我去恢复电力
I'm gonna get the power back on.
你去吧  我会处理叛徒
You do that. I know how to handle traitors.
安保警告
放下武器
Drop your weapons!
地下室
辛格
Singh.
千万别这样
You don't wanna do this.
这不是你的意愿
This isn't your will.
伊娃的意愿就是我的
Eva's will is my will.
保证成功
Success is assured.
烈日不是靠太阳能的吗
I thought Sunshine was solar-powered!
她怎么还能在夜里把人轰没了呢
How the frak is she frying people at night?
那些手环不是为了时髦
Those bracelets aren't fashion.
而是能量
They're fuel.
它们是太阳能电池组
They're solar energy battery packs.
我们怎么能把它们弄掉
Well, how do we get them off?
我们得要把内部的温度升高
We just gotta increase the internal temperature,
让电池过载  阿莱格拉  如果你...
overload the cells. Allegra, if you--
-已经在做了  -她不错啊
- Already on it. - She's good.
你准备做什么
What are you gonna do?
我也不知道  我是走一步看一步
I don't know. I'm making it up as I go.
伊丝丽兰萨  住手
你把我扔在铁山监狱自生自灭
而当卡夫来救我时
我孤身一人
我根本没有机会
而那...  是你的错  表妹
对我来说你屁都不是
明白了吗
好吧  动手吧
Fine. Do it.
你以为只有你有那种感觉吗
You think you're the only one that feels that way?
只有你感觉形单影只吗
The only one that feels alone?
后面排着去吧
Get in line!
好吧
Okay.
记得我告诉你有危险就炸石头吗
Remember when I told you if things go sideways, zap the stone?
-记得  -要我现在就用石头了
- Yeah. - I'd zap the stone.
你回来了
You came back.
哪能让你一个人爽呢
Couldn't let you have all the fun.
看来爽对富人完全是不一样的意思
Fun must mean something entirely different when you're rich.
宝贝...
Honey...
我回来了
I'm home.
看来有人忘了怎么单挑了
Guess somebody forgot to spike the punch.
我们把事情聊开吧
Let's talk about this.
聊什么
About what?
聊你是怎么把我的技术开发成武器
How you weaponized my technology?
敲诈有善心的捐献者
Extorted charitable donors?
绑架勒索无辜的超能力者
Kidnapped and blackmailed innocent meta-humans
像是纪美代  埃斯佩兰萨和米莉
like Kimiyo, Esperanza, and Millie?
这就是我的意思
This is me talking.
我都是迫不得已
I did what I had to do.
那我也就迫不得已了
Then I'll do what I have to do.
再见了  约瑟夫
Good-bye, Joseph.
别  伊娃  等等
No, Eva! Wait!
不
No!
你怎么就是不明白
What don't you understand?
他不值得去拯救
He's not worth saving!
也许...
Maybe...
但这不由你决定
But it's not your decision.
不  这事我决定了
Oh, yes, it is.
我丈夫...
My husband...
让我在那个世界备受折磨那么多年
let me rot in that world for years!
他不配活在这个世界里
He does not get to live in this one.
你不是我的妻子
You're not my wife.
我的妻子
My wife died
早就死在粒子加速器的爆炸中了
in the particle accelerator explosion.
可是...
Well...
我现在才像是活着
I've never felt more alive.
你甚至...
You're not...
都不是...
even....
人
human.
不  不要
No. No.
抱歉让你看到这一幕
I'm sorry you had to see that.
天啊
God!
你来干什么
What are you doing here?
我要走之前把这里搞定
I'm making this up as I go.
好吧
Right.
闪电侠  巴里
Flash. Barry.
我们不是敌人
You and I are not enemies.
从来就不是
We never have been.
你毫不留情地杀了他
You just killed him in cold blood.
你妻子想要抓一个坏人
Your wife set out to catch a bad man.
她做不到
She couldn't.
但我们联手  就有可能
But together, we could.
-我们是同一边的  -不
- We're on the same side. - No.
记住这一点
Just remember that.
好了  数到三  大家就动手
All right, on three, everybody go crazy.
明白
Got it.
听起来是个坏主意
That seems like bad advice.
是个歌名  不过我喜欢
Song title. No, I like it.
没事的  好了
It'll be good. All right.
一  二...
One, two...
都停下
Stand down.
约瑟夫已经死了
Joseph is dead.
这...
Well...
还真是没想到
I didn't see that coming.
你打算让我们离开吗
You're gonna let us go?
当然
Of course.
我今天的目标已经完成了
I've achieved my goal for today.
我们不会停止追捕你的
We'll never stop coming after you.
你们不会成功的
You'll fail.
这栋楼  这个公司...
This building, this company...
都是我的
It's all mine.
你和你的朋友们是非法入侵  所以...
And you and your little friends are trespassing, so...
快逃吧  巴里
run along now, Barry,
在我报警之前
before I have to call the police.
麦克洛奇夫人  您这段时间都在哪里
Mrs. McCulloch, where have you been all this time?
过去的六年里
Well, over the past six years,
我被一个国际犯罪团伙劫持
I have been held hostage by an international crime syndicate.
被迫看着他们窃取我的技术
Forced to watch as they stole my technology
去制造杀伤性武器
and used it to create deadly weapons.
您是如何逃脱的呢
How did you escape?
因为我的丈夫  约瑟夫
My husband, Joseph.
他不懈地努力寻找我
He worked tirelessly to try to find me.
终于成功找到了我...
And, um, he succeeded...
但我们重聚不久  他就遇害了
only to be murdered moments after we were reunited.
我的心痛之前无以言表
Words cannot express my sorrow.
但我将同中城警局一起
But know that I am working with the CCPD
找出杀害我丈夫的凶手
to try to find my husband's murderer.
而至于麦克洛奇技术公司
And as for McCulloch Technologies,
我将继续担任首席执行官
I will be resuming my position as CEO,
立即生效
effective immediately.
相信这也是约瑟夫想要看到的
It's what Joseph would have wanted.
谢谢大家
Thank you.
要去哪里吗
Going somewhere?
卡夫死了
Carver's dead,
意味着我的父母彻底安全了
which means my parents are finally free.
还有我也是
And so am I.
我要回家了
I'm going home.
苏  这我说不好
Sue, I'm not sure you can.
伊娃把卡夫之死...
Eva framed you...
栽赃给了你
for Carver's murder.
迪尔邦继承人身陷谋杀疑云而遭通缉
巴里  我们以前也有相似遭遇
Barry, we've been through stuff like this before.
别担心
Don't worry.
你会成功阻止伊娃并找回爱瑞丝的
You're gonna find a way to stop Eva and get Iris back.
我再也无法承受失去更多了...
I can't even be frustrated without, without losing more of it.
或许不要过分关注自己失去的
Maybe instead of focusing on what you've lost,
而是牢记你永远失去不了的
you should try remembering what you'll never lose.
比如你打败极速  神速和斯旺的原因
The reason you've beat Zoom, Godspeed, Thawne?
因为你靠的并不是速度
It's because speed isn't what drives you.
而是爱
It's love.
那才是你的源动力
That's your true force,
而那是什么都模仿不来的
and there is nothing artificial about that.
所以只要你坚持自我
So as long as you stay true to yourself,
就能成功打败那些坏人
you will always find a way to beat the bad guys.
还有坏女人
And gals.
我会想念你的
I'm gonna miss you.
我很快就会回来
I'll be back before you know it.
都准备好了吗
All set?
车已经在楼下等着了
Car's downstairs.
我保证会尽快把这两位
I promise I'll get these two back to you and your team
还回给你们团队
as soon as possible.
谢谢
Thanks.
好了
Okay.
冰霜也能听到我  对吗
Frost can hear me, too, right?
只要她醒着
As long as she's awake.
我醒着  真的
I'm awake. Really.
说吧
Go ahead.
一定要好起来
Just get better.
然后尽快回来
And hurry back.
我们激流勇进之旅还没去呢
We still have a whitewater rafting trip to take.
这可是你说的
I'm holding you to that.
她说她也很期待
She says she can't wait.
替我转告大家  我已经开始想念大家了
Tell the team I miss them already?
好的
I will.
-这是更安静些  -是啊
- This is a little quieter. - Yeah.
我知道自己...
Hey, look. I know that I'm...
不是很讨你喜欢
not your favorite person,
但如果你需要任何帮助
but if ever you need anything,
需要任何...我的咖啡
if you ever need my coffee.
不是说"我不喝咖啡"吗
What--what happened to, "I don't like coffee"?
好吧
Okay.
-谢谢你  -谢什么
- Thanks. - For what?
这个东西
For this.
当然
Of course.
这东西把她怎么了  我的表姐
What did it do to her? My cousin?
勾起了她最糟糕的回忆
It made her relive her worst memory.
你知道吗
You know what?
你留着
You hang on to it.
万一哪天你又需要它呢
Just in case you need it again.
二位
Hey, guys.
-你好  -谢谢大家能赶过来
- Hey. - Thanks for coming.
没事
Yeah.
爱瑞丝还有其他人
Iris and the others,
他们还被关在伊娃的监狱里
they're still Eva's prisoners.
我们得把他们救出来
We're gonna get them back.
而且记住  我们还拥有一件伊娃都没有的东西
And remember, we still have one thing that Eva doesn't.
希望
Hope.
我们还有增援
We also have reinforcements.
乔
Joe.
你还好吗
How are you here?
事实证明
Well, it turns out that
当那个想杀死你的家伙自己死了
when the guy that's trying to kill you kicks the bucket,
他们就取消了对我的保护
they lift the protection detail.
-很有道理  -纳什
- That makes sense. - Nash.
你好
Hey, man. Yeah.
-你好  -来得正好
- Hey. - And just in time.
团队现在正是最需要你的时候
Team needs you now more than ever.
让我们去救出我们所爱之人吧
Well, let's go save some people we love.
你已经鼓捣了几个小时了
You've been at this for hours.
巴里不是个容易放弃的人
Barry wouldn't give up,
他娶的这位也不会放弃
and the woman that he married wouldn't either.
监测到热能
温度98.9
热能已定位
我找到了
I found him.
在中城医院
at Central City Hospital
不敢相信我做到了
I can't believe I just did that.
我的天啊
Holy Frick.
爱瑞丝
Iris
爱瑞丝  别走
Iris, stay with me.
未完待续